reelgood.com 2019-12-24

# Privacy Policy | Reelgood

Reelgood collects some Personal Data from its Users.

## Owner and Data Controller

Reelgood  
48 Sycamore Street  
Apt 4  
San Francisco, CA 94110

 **Owner contact email:** support@reelgood.com

## Types of Data collected

Among the types of Personal Data that Reelgood collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookies; Usage Data; Universally unique identifier (UUID); Crash information; device information; email address; first name; last name; various types of Data; User ID; geographic position.

Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.  
Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using Reelgood.  
Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by Reelgood is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for Reelgood to provide its services. In cases where Reelgood specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.  
Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.  
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by Reelgood or by the owners of third-party services used by Reelgood serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy, if available.

Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through Reelgood and confirm that they have the third party's consent to provide the Data to the Owner.

## Mode and place of processing the Data

### Methods of processing

The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of Reelgood (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time.

### Legal basis of processing

The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:

  * Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note: Under some legislations the Owner may be allowed to process Personal Data until the User objects to such processing (“opt-out”), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Data is subject to European data protection law;
  * provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;
  * processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;
  * processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner;
  * processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.

In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

### Place

The Data is processed at the Owner's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located.

Depending on the User's location, data transfers may involve transferring the User's Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.

Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis of Data transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.

If any such transfer takes place, Users can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with the Owner using the information provided in the contact section.

### Retention time

Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for.

Therefore:

  * Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.
  * Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.

The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a legal obligation or upon order of an authority.

Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.

## The purposes of processing

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics, Registration and authentication, Infrastructure monitoring, Displaying content from external platforms, Managing contacts and sending messages, Contacting the User, Access to third-party accounts, Hosting and backend infrastructure, Interaction with external social networks and platforms, Beta Testing, Location-based interactions, Platform services and hosting, Traffic optimization and distribution and Remarketing and behavioral targeting.

Users can find further detailed information about such purposes of processing and about the specific Personal Data used for each purpose in the respective sections of this document.

## Facebook permissions asked by Reelgood

Reelgood may ask for some Facebook permissions allowing it to perform actions with the User's Facebook account and to retrieve information, including Personal Data, from it. This service allows Reelgood to connect with the User's account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook Inc.

For more information about the following permissions, refer to the[Facebook permissions documentation](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/facebook-login/permissions)and to the[Facebook privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).

The permissions asked are the following:

### Basic information

By default, this includes certain User’s Data such as id, name, picture, gender, and their locale. Certain connections of the User, such as the Friends, are also available. If the User has made more of their Data public, more information will be available.

### Contact email

Access the User's contact email address.

## Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

### Access to third-party accounts

This type of service allows Reelgood to access Data from your account on a third-party service and perform actions with it.  
These services are not activated automatically, but require explicit authorization by the User.

#### Facebook account access (Reelgood)

This service allows Reelgood to connect with the User's account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook, Inc.

Permissions asked: Contact email.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php). Privacy Shield participant.

### Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

#### MixPanel (MixPanel)

MixPanel is an analytics service provided by Mixpanel Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://mixpanel.com/legal/privacy-policy/)–[Opt Out](https://help.mixpanel.com/hc/en-us/articles/360000679006-Managing-Personal-Information#optout-users). Privacy Shield participant.

#### Google Analytics (Google LLC)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google LLC (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of Reelgood, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)–[Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). Privacy Shield participant.

### Beta Testing

This type of service makes it possible to manage User access to Reelgood, or parts of it, for the purpose of testing a certain feature or the entire Application.  
The service provider may automatically collect data related to crashes and statistics related to the User's use of Reelgood in a personally identifiable form.

#### Google Play Beta Testing (Google LLC)

Google Play Beta Testing is a beta testing service provided by Google LLC.

Personal Data collected: email address.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

### Contacting the User

#### Contact form (Reelgood)

By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes Reelgood to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.

Personal Data collected: email address; first name; last name; User ID; various types of Data.

#### Mailing list or newsletter (Reelgood)

By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning Reelgood. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to Reelgood or after making a purchase.

Personal Data collected: email address; first name; last name.

### Displaying content from external platforms

This type of service allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of Reelgood and interact with them.  
This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

#### YouTube video widget (Google LLC)

YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google LLC that allows Reelgood to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

#### Google Fonts (Google LLC)

Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google LLC that allows Reelgood to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

#### MyFonts (Monotype Imaging Inc.)

MyFonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Monotype Imaging Inc. that allows Reelgood to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://www.monotype.com/legal/privacy-policy).

### Hosting and backend infrastructure

This type of service has the purpose of hosting Data and files that enable Reelgood to run and be distributed as well as to provide a ready-made infrastructure to run specific features or parts of Reelgood. Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.

#### Algolia (Algolia SAS)

Algolia is a hosting and backend service provided by Algolia SAS.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: France –[Privacy Policy](https://www.algolia.com/policies/privacy/).

#### Amazon Web Services (AWS) (Amazon Web Services, Inc.)

Amazon Web Services (AWS) is a hosting and backend service provided by Amazon Web Services, Inc.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq/). Privacy Shield participant.

### Infrastructure monitoring

This type of service allows Reelgood to monitor the use and behavior of its components so its performance, operation, maintenance and troubleshooting can be improved.  
Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and mode of implementation of these services, whose function is to filter the activities of Reelgood.

#### Crashlytics (Google LLC)

Crashlytics is a monitoring service provided by Google LLC.

Personal Data collected: Crash information; device information; Universally unique identifier (UUID).

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

#### Pingdom (Pingdom AB)

Pingdom is a monitoring service provided by Pingdom AB.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data.

Place of processing: Sweden –[Privacy Policy](https://www.solarwinds.com/legal/privacy).

### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

This type of service allows interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of Reelgood.  
The interaction and information obtained through Reelgood are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.  
This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.  
It is recommended to log out from the respective services in order to make sure that the processed data on Reelgood isn’t being connected back to the User’s profile.

#### YouTube button and social widgets (Google LLC)

The YouTube button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the YouTube social network provided by Google LLC.

Personal Data collected: Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

#### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter, Inc.)

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

#### Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)

The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation). Privacy Shield participant.

### Location-based interactions

#### Non-continuous geolocation (Reelgood)

Reelgood may collect, use, and share User location Data in order to provide location-based services.  
Most browsers and devices provide tools to opt out from this feature by default. If explicit authorization has been provided, the User’s location data may be tracked by Reelgood.  
The geographic location of the User is determined in a manner that isn't continuous, either at the specific request of the User or when the User doesn't point out its current location in the appropriate field and allows the application to detect the position automatically.

Personal Data collected: geographic position.

### Managing contacts and sending messages

This type of service makes it possible to manage a database of email contacts, phone contacts or any other contact information to communicate with the User.  
These services may also collect data concerning the date and time when the message was viewed by the User, as well as when the User interacted with it, such as by clicking on links included in the message.

#### Mailchimp (The Rocket Science Group LLC)

Mailchimp is an email address management and message sending service provided by The Rocket Science Group LLC.

Personal Data collected: email address; first name; last name; various types of Data.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

#### Mandrill (The Rocket Science Group LLC)

Mandrill is an email address management and message sending service provided by The Rocket Science Group, LLC.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; email address; first name; last name; various types of Data.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

### Platform services and hosting

These services have the purpose of hosting and running key components of Reelgood, therefore allowing the provision of Reelgood from within a unified platform. Such platforms provide a wide range of tools to the Owner – e.g. analytics, user registration, commenting, database management, e-commerce, payment processing – that imply the collection and handling of Personal Data.  
Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.

#### WordPress.com (Automattic Inc.)

WordPress.com is a platform provided by Automattic Inc. that allows the Owner to build, run and host Reelgood.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/).

### Registration and authentication

By registering or authenticating, Users allow Reelgood to identify them and give them access to dedicated services.  
Depending on what is described below, third parties may provide registration and authentication services. In this case, Reelgood will be able to access some Data, stored by these third-party services, for registration or identification purposes.

#### Google OAuth (Google LLC)

Google OAuth is a registration and authentication service provided by Google LLC and is connected to the Google network.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

#### Facebook Authentication (Facebook, Inc.)

Facebook Authentication is a registration and authentication service provided by Facebook, Inc. and is connected to the Facebook social network.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/help/405977429438260). Privacy Shield participant.

### Remarketing and behavioral targeting

This type of service allows Reelgood and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of Reelgood by the User.  
This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using Cookies, information that is transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity.  
Some services offer a remarketing option based on email address lists.  
In addition to any opt-out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service's use of **cookies for certain remarketing features** by visiting the[Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).

 **Users may also opt-out of certain advertising features through applicable device settings, such as the device advertising settings for mobile phones or ads settings in general**.

#### Reelgood Anonymized Remarketing

We use your information to allow us or third parties to deliver ads based on your interests on our sites, affiliated sites or third party sites. Our retargeting activities abide by the NAI code of conduct.

### Traffic optimization and distribution

This type of service allows Reelgood to distribute their content using servers located across different countries and to optimize their performance.  
Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and the way these services are implemented. Their function is to filter communications between Reelgood and the User's browser.  
Considering the widespread distribution of this system, it is difficult to determine the locations to which the contents that may contain Personal Information User are transferred.

#### Cloudflare (Cloudflare Inc.)

Cloudflare is a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by Cloudflare Inc.  
The way Cloudflare is integrated means that it filters all the traffic through Reelgood, i.e., communication between Reelgood and the User's browser, while also allowing analytical data from Reelgood to be collected.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United States –[Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/).

## Further information about Personal Data

### Push notifications

Reelgood may send push notifications to the User to achieve the purposes outlined in this privacy policy.

Users may in most cases opt-out of receiving push notifications by visiting their device settings, such as the notification settings for mobile phones, and then change those settings for Reelgood, some or all of the apps on the particular device.  
Users must be aware that disabling push notifications may negatively affect the utility of Reelgood.

### Analysis and predictions based on the User’s Data (“profiling”)

The Owner may use the Personal and Usage Data collected through Reelgood to create or update User profiles. This type of Data processing allows the Owner to evaluate User choices, preferences and behaviour for the purposes outlined in the respective section of this document.  
User profiles can also be created through the use of automated tools like algorithms, which can also be provided by third parties. To find out more, about the profiling activities performed, Users can check the relevant sections of this document.  
The User always has a right to object to this kind of profiling activity. To find out more about the User's rights and how to exercise them, the User is invited to consult the section of this document outlining the rights of the User.

### Personal Data collected through sources other than the User

The Owner of Reelgood may have legitimately collected Personal Data relating to Users without their knowledge by reusing or sourcing them from third parties on the grounds mentioned in the section specifying the legal basis of processing.  
Where the Owner has collected Personal Data in such a manner, Users may find specific information regarding the source within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.

### The Service is not directed to children under the age of 13

Users declare themselves to be adult according to their applicable legislation. Minors may use Reelgood only with the assistance of a parent or guardian. Under no circumstance persons under the age of 13 may use Reelgood.

### Unique device identification

Reelgood may track Users by storing a unique identifier of their device, for analytics purposes or for storing Users' preferences.

### User identification via a universally unique identifier (UUID)

Reelgood may track Users by storing a so-called universally unique identifier (or short UUID) for analytics purposes or for storing Users' preferences. This identifier is generated upon installation of this Application, it persists between Application launches and updates, but it is lost when the User deletes the Application. A reinstall generates a new UUID.

## The rights of Users

Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.

In particular, Users have the right to do the following:

  *  **Withdraw their consent at any time.** Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
  *  **Object to processing of their Data.** Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below.
  *  **Access their Data.** Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.
  *  **Verify and seek rectification.** Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.
  *  **Restrict the processing of their Data.** Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.
  *  **Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed.** Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
  *  **Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller.** Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User's consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.
  *  **Lodge a complaint.** Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.

### Details about the right to object to processing

Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.

Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.

### How to exercise these rights

Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.

## Additional information about Data collection and processing

### Legal action

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of Reelgood or the related Services.  
The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

### Additional information about User's Personal Data

In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, Reelgood may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

### System logs and maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, Reelgood and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with Reelgood (System logs) use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose.

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.

### How “Do Not Track” requests are handled

Reelgood does not support “Do Not Track” requests.  
To determine whether any of the third-party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page and possibly within Reelgood and/or - as far as technically and legally feasible - sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.

Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required.

### Definitions and legal references

#### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.

#### Usage Data

Information collected automatically through Reelgood (or third-party services employed in Reelgood), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use Reelgood, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.

#### User

The individual using Reelgood who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.

#### Data Subject

The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

#### Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.

#### Data Controller (or Owner)

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of Reelgood. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of Reelgood.

#### Reelgood (or this Application)

The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.

#### Service

The service provided by Reelgood as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/application.

#### European Union (or EU)

Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area.

#### Cookies

Small sets of data stored in the User's device.

#### Legal information

This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation).

This privacy policy relates solely to Reelgood, if not stated otherwise within this document.

Latest update: October 31, 2019
